Our first guest tonight is a three-time
Golden Globe winner and two-time penguin
who now joins a storied roster of LA TV
detectives. Sugar returns Friday to
Apple TV. Please welcome Colin Farrell.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Good to see [cheering] you.
>> Good to see you, man.
>> Hello Sarah Nemitz. She's great, right
Sarah?
>> Yeah, wonderful, yeah.
>> Colin said hello Sarah. I don't know if
you could hear him.
>> Hello Sarah Nemitz. [laughter]
>> Good to see you.
>> How's it Guillermo's over there too if
you want to say hi.
>> How are you? Good.
>> You look great.
>> You look great. You look fantastic.
>> Where did you keep six-pack today
Guillermo?
>> Thank you.
>> [laughter]
>> How you doing?
>> I'm well.
>> Yeah. You
I was going to mention that I'm having a
difficult week because we have you here
and we have Will Ferrell here and
Ferrell and Ferrell
>> shaky start to that that sentiment you
were sharing there.
>> It's a shaky week because you're here.
>> Well, but Will Ferrell
>> It has nothing to do with you.
>> where you're go where you go with this.
>> Ferrell Ferrell
>> Yeah, man, it happens.
>> It's confusing especially if you have an
like you have a New York accent, you
have whatever.
>> Colin Farrell, Will Ferrell, it's the
same.
>> Now you say it it sounds exactly the
>> Uh cuz I put on a little American accent
cuz I'm an actor and that's what
sometimes I do.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay, where's my dialect coach on speed
dial? Um
>> Now I know it's Farrell.
>> Which one? That's you? Farrell. That's
how I say
>> And then Farrell.
>> Like rrr
>> Like the S, the animal.
>> yeah.
Like the raccoon that had its way with
him in Elf.
>> [laughter]
>> I wish I was Will Ferrell. I would love
to have Elf on my CV.
>> [laughter]
>> When we think of him, we'll just think
of a raccoon, yeah. Hopefully with
rabies or something.
>> give it that rrr
>> [laughter]
>> Have you been and I know this maybe this
is racial profiling but because I know
you're from Europe.
>> Let's go there.
>> Have you been watching the World Cup?
>> Yes.
>> Yes, okay.
>> No, I I was try I was in New York with
my son this weekend so I just watched
the highlights.
>> You did?
>> Yeah, but we were there for the Knicks
winning the the NBA final.
>> YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
>> [cheering]
>> A LOT OF NEW YORKERS HERE IN LA.
>> IT'S A WEIRD THING. WELL, first of all
yeah, there are a lot of New Yorkers
here in LA. I'm one of them myself but
>> Surprisingly you didn't cheer. You're
the only one that didn't cheer to that.
>> I cheered when I was game. Yeah.
>> It was amazing to be there for it.
>> Did you go out and go out in the streets
and get crazy?
>> were having a steak dinner but across
the road was a bodega and they had a TV
screen stuck to the wall outside and
there was about a hundred people there
and they just lost their when they won.
Yeah, it was amazing. But we didn't go.
We stayed away from the the anarchy.
>> Have you a sporting event back home in
Ireland that has been comparable to
that? The reaction
>> Italia '90, the World Cup Italia '90.
Ireland played and we got to the
we got to the quarterfinals against
Italy.
We beat Romania in the second round
in a penalty shootout.
It was bliss. The whole country went
bananas. It was bliss. It was a long
time coming. We didn't have a much of a
track record in the World Cup so
>> Italy was playing in Italy at that time.
>> the World Cup was in Italy. Italy were
playing in Italy and we were playing
Romania in the second round and it went
it went it went 90 minutes without a
goal.
Penalty shootout and it came down to the
last penalty and David O'Leary put the
ball in the back of the net and the
whole country was just up in arms and I
was out in the streets and all the women
were like
I was 14.
>> [cheering and applause]
>> It was amazing. Yeah, I remember jumping
on a 14 in the town that I lived in the
village that I lived in Castleknock
jumping on the bonnet hood of a car
as it was going by cuz there was people
hanging out of it. I just jumped on the
bonnet hood of the car
but unfortunately
there were green lights for the next 2
miles.
So, [laughter] I ended up 11:00 at night
at 14 in Blanchardstown, the next town
over. I mean, it wasn't a long walk
home, and it was a
>> [laughter]
>> somewhat joyful chaotic walk home.
>> Did you jump on a car?
>> Nobody was getting stomped on, and they
let, you know, There was no school buses
set on fire.
>> buses. That's what I was going to ask
you about. If somebody lit a school bus
on fire, would the people have been
disturbed by that or
>> churches would be full again. There'd be
an awful amount of guilt on the island.
>> I see. I see.
>> An awful amount of guilt.
>> I see. All right.
>> Someone's going to be having a hefty
confession.
>> [laughter]
>> I know you
>> your name is
>> I know you are a Formula 1 fan.
>> I love the Formula 1. What about you?
>> of a team sport. Not not that interested
in it, to be honest.
>> Yeah, but there's no team sport where
the two team members are as vehemently
competing with each other, against each
other. Essentially, you know, right?
>> when when
team orders come into play, particularly
if one driver is doing a lot better than
the other driver in the team
championship.
>> You got to block guys out, right?
>> Yeah, and you all that kind of stuff.
>> You got to ride along in one of these
vehicles.
>> in Miami a few weeks ago. I went to the
F1. It was the first time in 20 years
I'd been, and we did a what they call a
hot lap. Yeah.
>> You'd never done that before.
>> lot scarier than that other thing, Hot
Wings, I did a few years ago.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> never did it before. I've never been in
a car when it's been driven right at the
limit of its capability, you know.
>> you just came up with a great show idea
for Sean Evans. He gets behind the wheel
>> 180 miles an hour.
>> while he while he eats Hot Wings.
>> Wings. Yes. I love this idea. But you
brought a video and well, this is what
the show would look like. I love it.
>> not bring this video, by the way. The
researchers found this video.
>> Oh, is that right? Somebody brought this
video, but enjoy it nonetheless.
>> Holy
Oh my god. You got him on the inside,
man. You got him on THE APEX. GOOD MAN.
I MEAN, THAT'S JUST UNBELIEVABLE. I feel
like I'm going to have a heart attack,
but in a good way. Oh my god, man. Oh my
good lord. Wow, look at that. I've seen
this on television so many times.
>> Got a big straight.
late breaking.
What
sweet mother Jesus.
>> Wow. Oh my god, that was just
extraordinary.
Holy cow. How old are you?
>> [cheering]
>> Well, I asked him how old he was.
>> A really good question.
>> I was just going to I was about to card
him.
>> It's a question I would have asked when
I got into the
>> into the car, not at the end. Yeah,
yeah. Have you got your driver's
license?
>> It looked like you were
You were giving your nephew a driving
lesson or something like that. That was
a good kid, right?
>> Yeah, he did look about 16, but I think
he's doing very well in Formula 2, I
believe.
>> Really?
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah. He was terrifying.
>> Yeah, that seems even more terrifying.
So, this sport that you love, you're you
were scared to go along with it.
>> Passenger seat.
>> Passenger seat. If you were driving,
would that be more or less
>> a go. I mean, the car would have been in
the first wall if I was driving. The
control he had was astonishing. I mean,
it just felt very, very awkward.
>> It felt like the car was about to fall
apart, but he was in complete control
the whole time. Even when it felt like
we were skidding out of control, he was
just adjusting and going back the other
direction, and it was mad.
>> Yeah, I mean, you put a lot of trust in
that 13-year-old boy driving you.
>> [laughter]
>> Well, we're going to take a break. When
we come back, we're going to see a clip
from a Colin show, Sugar. Colin Farrell
is here with us. We'll be right back.
>> Maybe someone else stayed behind.
Second group, third wave, California.
John Sugar.
I'm still here if anyone else is.
It'd be
It'd be nice to [music] talk to someone.
>> That is Colin Farrell in Sugar,
which [cheering] you can see on Apple TV
season 2 premieres on Friday.
Okay.
Set alien no you said alien so I I
didn't want to say alien in case people
have not caught up but you've said it
and so now let's go with it.
That was the twist in the middle of the
first season that
character was like blue a traditional LA
detective it seemed it would have seemed
is actually an alien.
But still doing his job.
That's Batman and loves human beings. I
mean what's not to love? Just turn on
just turn on the news. What's not to
love?
So good to each other but he does that's
one of the lovely things about playing
him is that he
he's an eternal optimist in a way he
does love he sees all the ugliness and
all the cruelty and all the violence but
he also sees the extraordinary
generosity and decency and compassion
and tenderness that human beings are so
capable of as well which is why it's so
crushing when he encounters it's
opposite you know but that's That's one
of the lovely things about playing the
character it really is going to work and
it like as opposed to Penguin and I know
it's acting and but you take it home
with you a little bit and Penguin who
was so kind of wicked and wickedly
psychopathic and
an absolute malignant narcissist this
guy is just kind to his core. When you
say you take it home with you you ever
keep the Penguin makeup on and like
go someplace? the first time we did a
makeup test I went to Starbucks yeah. Oh
you did? Yeah.
Yeah. And did people look at you funny?
No soy latte you know that kind of
thing.
They they yeah yeah yeah I got a few I
got a few looks yeah for sure. What name
did you nobody knew nobody had a
reference cuz it was before the first
film so it had never been put on screen
or anything but
no I said Oz yeah. Uh-huh. Yeah yeah
yeah and what's the name sir? Oz yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> And I waited for me. spell it right? Did
they get it yeah they did it. yeah they
did.
Pretty easy. Penguin's going to be in
the Batman movie in the new Batman movie
right? Yeah yeah, yeah.
>> [cheering and applause]
>> Yeah.
>> That's exciting.
>> Yeah, I've only got a couple of scenes,
but the script is script is amazing.
Which is great that I only have a couple
of scenes cuz it means the film isn't
ruined for me. I can watch it now as an
audience member and actually enjoy it.
>> you did reread the whole script? You
>> Read the whole script. They were kind
enough to give me the whole script and
not just the pages I was in, yeah. And
it's extraordinary.
>> Is it an assortment of villains or is
there one main
>> I can't. No, there that's when I get
fired. Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah. So, I'll
just say it's really, really good.
>> I was already surprised you told me how
much you're in it and
I figured I'd go for a little bit more
if I could.
>> It sounds slurry.
>> that you um
you First I want to mention this
photograph because you were with
screen you were at a screening that Tom
Cruise put together for Steven
Spielberg's movie Disclosure Day and
there's you, Dakota Fanning, and Tom
Cruise. And this while it may look like
Steven, it is a popcorn bucket.
>> Where Steven the popcorn was in Steven's
brain. Is it supposed to be Steven cuz
it looks like he's way on holidays, like
he's got a tan.
>> Yeah, he's a tan Steven, but he's filled
with you know, he's filled with popcorn
so that'll heat you up a little bit. Is
this Did Tom actually eat out of this
thing?
>> He did, yeah. He loves his popcorn and
when he goes to the cinema he loves the
whole experience.
>> How do you know Tom? Could from working
together?
>> We did Minority Report lifetime ago.
Yeah, like
and and times [applause and cheering]
years ago. Does he
Did he make a big impression on you when
when you met him for the first time?
>> He's an animal.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah. Oh my god, what an engine that guy
>> He is something else.
>> What an engine, honestly. He's such an
impressive human being. I mean, he's an
extraordinary actor and I I I had a
friend a few years ago that was in that
was only 23 or 24 and they only knew him
from the Mission Impossible films and I
was fortunate to get to show this friend
some of his earlier stuff like Rain Man
and Born on the 4th of July and he's
just Tom is an extraordinary actor who
has who has chosen to veer into more
popcorn multiplex suited fare like
Mission Impossible, but it's a conscious
but he's he's just brilliant anything he
turns his hand to he's extraordinary and
working with him. I mean he's healthily
competitive as you can imagine you know,
he'd walk onto the set and he remember
one day he walked onto the set and he
said is this an action movie? Why don't
I hear action? I was kind of like all
right, let's go.
>> Oh.
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah, he's like
let's go you know,
>> [laughter]
>> he's
one of the most positive energies I've
ever been around.
>> we're he's been here on this show and I
distinctly remember them telling us hey
Tom we got to make sure we're on time
cuz Tom's got to get out of here. He's
got to go do this thing or whatever. I'm
like yeah, yeah, yeah, no problem. And
we went to commercial break. He went out
in the audience and 30 minutes later he
came back to his seat.
>> Really?
>> Yeah, he was out talking to every single
person in the audience.
>> isn't he?
>> Yeah, you're not going to do that
tonight.
>> No, I just want to keep everyone away
from me.
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> Keep them away.
Where's my Where's my security?
>> Listen,
>> [applause]
>> there's only one Tom Cruise.
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Thank God
the planet couldn't handle a second one.
He's amazing, man. It's great to see
him. I hadn't seen him in a long time.
It's lovely to see
>> How'd you like that Disclosure day?
>> Brilliant. I mean I just love Spielberg.
I was raised by somebody else.
>> approved?
>> As an alien I with blue eyes.
>> Uh-huh, you approved?
>> Colin Firth using the alien tech. I know
Colin's human and then Colin Firth, Will
Ferrell, Pharrell Williams. It's all
very confusing. Um
But yeah, yeah, yeah, well I was raised
you know on Steven's stuff and I just
love his work and I was thrilled to see
the film loved it.
>> Well, it's great to see you.
Congratulations the show is Sugar it's
season two.
>> Thanks everyone.
>> Premiering Friday on Apple TV. COLIN
>> [cheering]
>> FARRELL EVERYBODY we'll be back with
Justin Timberlake Williams.